<ModMetaData>
	<name>Alpha Biomes</name>
	<author>Sarg</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.0</li>
		<li>1.1</li>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/AndroidQuazar/VanillaExpandedFramework</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>BiomesTeam.BiomesIslands</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>

	</loadAfter>

	<packageId>sarg.alphabiomes</packageId>
	<description>Adds multiple unique new biomes to Rimworld.

&lt;size=24&gt;Features&lt;/size&gt;

Adds 12 new diverse biomes to your Rimworlds. The mod has been designed with the Alpha Animals mod in mind, although it is not a requirement.

- The Mycotic Jungle: a warm and humid biome filled with HUGE mushrooms. Home to the Wildpod and some weird mushroom varieties of usual creatures.
- The Gallatross Graveyard: an arid temperate biome, littered with the skeletal remains of ancient beasts.
- The Feralisk Infested Jungle: a warm, wet biome with incredibly dense vegetation, filled to the brink with extremely dangerous predatory spiders.
- The Ocular Forest: a weird transdimensional realm intruding upon our Universe. Home to strange new flora and fauna.
- The Gelatinous Superorganism: a swampy biome that is actually the upper surface of an extraordinarily large mold-like creature. No rocks to be found, but plenty of food.
- The Mechanoid Intrusion: a desolate temperate biome with mechanical ruins. Apparently an ancient mechanoid attempt at turning the planet into a megastructure.
- The Propane Lakes: a frozen wasteland, colder than the most inhospitable Sea Ice, but teaming with aberrant flora and fauna.
- The Forsaken Crags: permanently clouded by a preternatural darkness, light is the most valuable commodity in this desertic landscape. Inspired by (and compatible with) the Forsakens mod.
- The Tar Pits: an arid biome rich in vegetation, filled with treacherous tar pits that make movement quite difficult. Beware the Bumbledrone hives! 
- The Pyroclastic Conflagration: a volcanic expanse of unrelenting and brutal nature. Fire and lava are both your worst enemy and your best friend in this biome.
- The Idyllic Meadows: a lush meadow of giant flowers. A super easy biome that provides tons of resources and few predators.
- The Miasmic Mangrove: a dangerous tropical biome full of debilitating diseases.


The biomes have been tweaked so they don't take too much space in the world map, and you might have to generate a planet again if some biome is not appearing, since they have different temperature and humidity characteristics.

&lt;size=24&gt;Issues&lt;/size&gt;

Balance is obviously always a concern, although it has been playtested. Feel free to tell me if you think something is too wacky.

&lt;size=24&gt;Plans for the future&lt;/size&gt;

Maybe more biomes, who knows!

&lt;size=24&gt;Compatibility&lt;/size&gt;

Compatible with any other biome mod 
Compatible with Alpha Animals (obviously)
Compatible with Magical Menagerie
Compatible with Dinosauria
Compatible with Megafauna
Compatible with Animal Collab Project
Compatible with Vanilla Animals Expanded
Compatible with Rim of Madness - Bones
Compatible with Vanilla Fishing Expanded (adds 19 new fish)
Compatible with Fish Industry
Compatible with Forsakens
Compatible with Camouflage and Stealth
Compatible with Fertile Fields

Mods that modify the way the world is generated MAY cause some weird results. Use at your own risk.

&lt;size=24&gt;Credit&lt;/size&gt;
Bone planet: Hyptosis https://opengameart.org/content/bone-planet 
Some sounds by Mike Koenig at http://soundbible.com
Alien planet sound modified from Speedenza: https://freesound.org/people/Speedenza/sounds/198532/

&lt;size=24&gt;Changelog&lt;/size&gt;

v2.8: Added two new biomes. (26/06/22)
Full changelog on GitHub


	</description>
</ModMetaData>
