<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Rabbie The Moonrabbit race</name>
	<author>Runne Latki</author>
	<supportedVersions>
        <li>1.3</li>
        <li>1.4</li>
        <li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
   	<packageId>RunneLatki.RabbieRaceMod.sk</packageId>
    <modDependencies>
        <li>
            <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
            <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races 2.0</displayName>
            <steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
            <downloadUrl>https://github.com/erdelf/AlienRaces/wiki</downloadUrl>
        </li>
    </modDependencies>
    <loadAfter>
        <li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
        <li>JecsTools</li>
        <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
        <li>CETeam.CombatExtended</li>
        <li>skyarkhangel.HSK</li>
    </loadAfter>
	<description>

    Rabbie The MoonRabbit Race

    As you can see in the night sky, the moon exists in the Rimworld. And there are residents in the moon.
    Rabbbies are races that migrate from moon to moon beyond the universe.
    With a brilliant brain and close to Glitterworlds technology, they are prospering all universe by building a giant arcology, the moon city.

     +Rabbie is smart and smart, and stands out in intellectual activities like research + 
     -But they're mentally unstable, so they have higher mentalbreak threshhold - 
     -and are more severely affected by Psychic waves - 
     +Due to the long history of war, combat skills have been developed, allowing fast shooting and more accuracy + 
     +They have also developed the ability to safely treat and operate on injured people and to synth drugs + 
     -However, because of their weak body structure, they are very vulnerable to melee combat. - 
     -they have lower carrying capacity and the lower speed of mining - 

      Planetarium  

    Long ago, the ancestors of Rabbie who were migrating were captured by Transcendent Planet and genetically manipulated throughout the Spaceship, they got excellent intellectual abilities, but in the absence of a special substance called Planetarium, they became lunatic.

    The only places where Rabbitish empires can migrate are rare planets that can harvest planetarium. It is mostly because of the Planetarium that the soldiers of the empire and the Dept.Energysupply staffs come down to the planet and cause friction with Planet's natives or civilizations.
    Rabbies are also enjoying this material, commonly called  'Spice' . A refined Planetarium can also be consumed, but it will give you a richer scent when you drink it with tea or cocktails and keep your more mental clearer.
    Rabbie, who has consumed planetarium for a long time, is said to have the ability to see a blurry but short future and have an amazing shooting ability.

    You can also replenish Planetarium, at least in part, by ingesting Braincrystal-the nervous system in which planetarium is crystallized-which can be found when you open the head of a deceased Rabbie. It's a scary story.
    Wherever Rabbies are, saving planetarium will be a top priority. Otherwise, you may have a terrible ending.

      New faction, Rabbitish Empire  
    The Rabbitish empire migrates to the moons of several planets for a long time to build a city, but because of its long distance, it cuts off from the empires of the previous universe and elects a new empress of the universe.
    The Rabbitish empire's policy on the planet depends on Empress's thinking and the development of the moon city.
    Rabbitish Soldiers and scientists on the planet are in duty of the enormous energy and planetarium needs of the moon city and its citizens.
    They may be exclusive or hostile at first, but they will usually be indifferent if they feel not threatening to their work or if you are cooperative.

    Make hostile impressions on them, or do not let your forces feel threats to them.
    If your settlement is both, be careful! The Rabbitish Empire is a country with a lot of war experience. They have been at war with the inhabitants of various planets, and victory against many of civilizations. If they think you threaten the empire, you'll be attacked with advanced technology.
    do not recommend shooting against them like line-infantry. because it's the beneficial combat of the Rabbitish Empire. They will be relatively weak before melee.
    Their army consists of a field army of Rabbie citizens and a regular army descending in space with power armor.

      Two Storytellers  
    Cele Jackrabbit - Cele Jackrabbit is a senior officer in the Rabbitish Empire. Drink spice tea together in her flagship, and carefully listen to the War of the Rabbitish Empire and the history of blood (most events are replaced by raids, increasing in difficulty and preparing for war. )

    Luna Jackrabbit - (Coming soon) Cele's sister, Luna, is Scientist of Dept.energysupply. She is working to cure the mental problems that Rabbie race has brought down from now on. she say quiet and clearly, but you will be listens to increasingly confusing and scary stories.

      etc  
     Various Pawn Customizing 
     Various ability-enhancing clothing 
     Over 120 backstories 

    Rabbie race mod allows you to customize your pawn by combining different pretty outfits and colors.
    Give your pawns a unique personality by mixing different face, ear shapes and hairstyles.
    All Rabbie apparel also fit perfectly with vanilla outfits, with proper in-game balancing.

    Rabbie race mod seeks to enrich the enjoyment of vanilla play.
    Rabbie's equipment is expensive and requires a long time to craft, and you will still need vanilla weapons and equipment to survive.
    Also, other clothing and equipment mods can be used naturally.

  </description>
</ModMetaData>