<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>

	<!--===================== Concepts taught through the learning readout, when opportunities arise ===================-->

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>FD_Shields</defName>
		<label>FD: Shield Generators</label>
		<priority>50</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
		<helpText>Shields stop incoming projectiles at the cost of battery power.  They don't stop people from moving through them, however.  They use a low amount of power when idle and draw increased power when stopping incoming fire.\n\nIt is recommended to use batteries, as shields have a very high instant power draw.  Automatic and sustained fire will drain power faster so multiple batteries are recommended.
		</helpText>
		<highlightTags>
			<li>FD_Shields</li>
		</highlightTags>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>FD_CoilTemperature</defName>
		<label>FD: Shield Coil Temperature</label>
		<priority>50</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
		<helpText>Shield coils heat up as the shield absorbs incoming projectiles.  The generator will slowly exchange that heat with the room it's in until it reaches ambient temperature.\n\nOver 100C: Minor failure, shield can cause shorts on the power network.\n\nOver 150C: Moderate failure, shields can cause shorts and might breakdown.\n\n Over 200C: Critical failure, shield will short, breakdown, and suffer damage in an explosion.
		</helpText>
		<highlightTags>
			<li>FD_CoilTemperature</li>
		</highlightTags>
	</ConceptDef>

	<ConceptDef>
		<defName>FD_ShieldsPortable</defName>
		<label>FD: Portable Shield Generators</label>
		<priority>50</priority>
		<needsOpportunity>True</needsOpportunity>
		<helpText>Portable Shields are miniaturizable emplacements which allow you to move the generator for your purposes.  They come with a small internal battery which can power the unit as a standalone.\n\nIt can be connected to a normal power grid and will act as a normal battery.  These shields have a fixed projection radius.
		</helpText>
		<highlightTags>
			<li>FD_ShieldsPortable</li>
		</highlightTags>
	</ConceptDef>

</Defs>
