<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Planetarium Intake Form Reaction: Refined Powder -->

  <RefinedPlanetarium.label>Refined Planetarium</RefinedPlanetarium.label>
  <RefinedPlanetarium.description>A mineral substance refined from particulate in the atmosphere scattered by volcanic activity.
  \n\nPlanetarium is vital for rabbie survival, for without it they eventually descend into madness. While stimulating activity in the brain, rabbies that consume the substance for a long time begin to have brief prophetic visions; seeing seconds into the future.
  \n\nCommonly refered to as spice, the substance is highly addictive to non-rabbies as well, but only rabbies have been found to experience prophetic visions. Regardless, consumption of the substance generally imparts an enjoyable euphoric sensation.</RefinedPlanetarium.description>
  <RefinedPlanetarium.labelNoun>Refined Planetarium</RefinedPlanetarium.labelNoun>


  <!-- Planetarium Intake Form Response: Brainstorm -->

  <Braincrystal.label>Rabbie Braincrystal</Braincrystal.label>
  <Braincrystal.description>A semisolid cystal substance found inside the heads of rabbies.
  \n\nContains trace amounts of planetarium, which can soothe cravings for the substance, but is disgusting and disturbing to eat.</Braincrystal.description>
  <Braincrystal.labelNoun>Rabbie Braincrystal</Braincrystal.labelNoun>


  <!-- Planetarium Intake Form Response: Planetarium Tea -->

  <PlanetariumTea.label>Planetarium Tea</PlanetariumTea.label>
  <PlanetariumTea.description>A fragrant tea of boiled planetarium. The most common method of planetarium consumption, in provides more enjoyment compared to consuming raw planetarium.</PlanetariumTea.description>
  <PlanetariumTea.labelNoun>Planetarium Tea</PlanetariumTea.labelNoun>


  <!-- Labyrinth Planetarium In Bloom -->

  <Whisperofplanet.label>Whisper of the Planet</Whisperofplanet.label>
  <Whisperofplanet.description>A phenomenon that only appears in the Rabbie race. Rabbies who have consumed the planetarium for long periods of time have the ability to glimpse into the future a few seconds in tense situations. When active, the Rabbies' eyes will change colors. This alongisde the Rabbies' formidable shooting skills makes them a formidably dangerous race on the battlefield.</Whisperofplanet.description>
  <Whisperofplanet.comps.HediffComp_Discoverable.discoverLetterLabel>Planetarium Visions</Whisperofplanet.comps.HediffComp_Discoverable.discoverLetterLabel>
  <Whisperofplanet.comps.HediffComp_Discoverable.discoverLetterText>{0} hears the whisper of the planet. \n\nAs a result of prolonged planetarium intake, this Rabbie has gained the ability to glimpse into the future, although imperfectly.</Whisperofplanet.comps.HediffComp_Discoverable.discoverLetterText>

  <!-- Planetarium poisoning -->

  <PlanetariumAddiction.label>Planetarium Addiction</PlanetariumAddiction.label>
  <PlanetariumAddiction.description>Trace amounts of planetarium exists in the body. When planetarium levels drop to dangerous levels, cognitive function declines. Recovery from planetarium addiction is impossible.</PlanetariumAddiction.description>  
  <PlanetariumAddiction.comps.HediffComp_Discoverable.discoverLetterLabel>Planetarium Addiction</PlanetariumAddiction.comps.HediffComp_Discoverable.discoverLetterLabel>
  <PlanetariumAddiction.comps.HediffComp_Discoverable.discoverLetterText>{0} has consumed planetarium and gained an addiction to the substance. Recovery from the addiction is impossible, but with sustained dosages they will not experience any downsides.</PlanetariumAddiction.comps.HediffComp_Discoverable.discoverLetterText>
  <PlanetariumAddiction.stages.Lunatic.label>Madness</PlanetariumAddiction.stages.Lunatic.label>


</LanguageData>