<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- 래비 속옷 -->

  <RB_Camisole.label>Rabbie Camisole</RB_Camisole.label>
  <RB_Camisole.description>A simple set of camisole and panties made to fit rabbies.</RB_Camisole.description>


  <!-- 래비 캐주얼 티셔츠 = 티셔츠+발목 바지 -->

  <RB_CasualTshirt.label>Rabbie Casual T-Shirt</RB_CasualTshirt.label>
  <RB_CasualTshirt.description>A simple set of pants and t-shirt made to fit rabbies.</RB_CasualTshirt.description>


  <!-- 래비 실내용 앞치마 -->

  <RB_Apron.label>Rabbie Apron</RB_Apron.label>
  <RB_Apron.description>A simple apron made to fit rabbies.</RB_Apron.description>


  <!-- 래비 토끼후드 바람막이 -->

  <RB_Earjacket.label>Rabbie Hoodie</RB_Earjacket.label>
  <RB_Earjacket.description>A hooded jacket made to fit rabbies. The hood has ear-shaped pockets to keep long ears warm.</RB_Earjacket.description>


  <!-- 래비 리본셔츠 = 끈리본셔츠 주름치마 오버니 -->

  <RB_Casualribbonshirt.label>Rabbie Ribboned Shirt</RB_Casualribbonshirt.label>
  <RB_Casualribbonshirt.description>A simple outfit composed of a skirt, buttoned shirt and a ribbon, made to fit rabbies.</RB_Casualribbonshirt.description>


  <!-- 래비 별 점퍼 -->

  <RB_Starjacket.label>Rabbie Jacket</RB_Starjacket.label>
  <RB_Starjacket.description>A sporty jacket made to fit rabbies.</RB_Starjacket.description>


  <!-- 래비 넥타이셔츠 = 넥타이셔츠 주름치마 맨다리 -->

  <RB_Casualtieshirt.label>Rabbie Tie Shirt</RB_Casualtieshirt.label>
  <RB_Casualtieshirt.description>A simple outfit composed of a skirt, buttoned shirt and a tie, made to fit rabbies.</RB_Casualtieshirt.description>


  <!-- 래비 블레이저 -->

  <RB_Blazer.label>Rabbie Blazer</RB_Blazer.label>
  <RB_Blazer.description>A sharp looking blazer made to fit rabbies.</RB_Blazer.description>


  <!-- 래비 여름옷 = 상의+짧바지 -->

  <RB_Summerfit.label>Rabbie Summer Clothes</RB_Summerfit.label>
  <RB_Summerfit.description>A tank top and shorts combination made to fit rabbies. Designed to keep the wearer cool in hot conditions.</RB_Summerfit.description>


  <!-- 래비 여름 가디건 = 시스루 여름가디건 -->

  <RB_Summerouter.label>Rabbie Summer Cardigan</RB_Summerouter.label>
  <RB_Summerouter.description>A thin cardigan made to fit rabbies. Helps insulate the wearer from heat.</RB_Summerouter.description>


  <!-- 래비 흰챙 여름모자 -->

  <RB_Summerhat.label>Rabbie Summer Hat</RB_Summerhat.label>
  <RB_Summerhat.description>A wide brim hat adorned with a ribbon. Keeps the wearer cool against the harsh summer sun.</RB_Summerhat.description>


  <!-- 래비 겨울 스웨터 = 목폴라니트+치마+스타킹 -->

  <RB_Winterknit.label>Rabbie Sweater</RB_Winterknit.label>
  <RB_Winterknit.description>A knitted sweater made to fit rabbies. Helps keep the wearer warm during cold conditions.</RB_Winterknit.description>


  <!-- 래비 겨울극지 파카 = 털달린 파카 -->

  <RB_Winterouter.label>Rabbie Parka</RB_Winterouter.label>
  <RB_Winterouter.description>A thick, fur collared parka made to fit rabbies. Helps keep the wearer warm during cold conditions.</RB_Winterouter.description>


  <!-- 래비 겨울 털뭉치모자 -->

  <RB_Winterhat.label>Rabbie Hood</RB_Winterhat.label>
  <RB_Winterhat.description>A thick hood cap. Great for keeping warm in the winter.</RB_Winterhat.description>


  <!-- 금속냄비 -->

  <RB_Metalpot.label>Rabbie Metal Pot</RB_Metalpot.label>
  <RB_Metalpot.description>It's a metal pot. Supposedly better head protection that nothing at all, if you were desperate.</RB_Metalpot.description>


  <!-- 래비 멋내기 리본 -->

  <RB_Headribbon.label>Rabbie Ribbon (Head)</RB_Headribbon.label>
  <RB_Headribbon.description>A ribbon to be worn in ones hair. Offers no protection whatsoever, but it looks cute; so people might like the wearer more.</RB_Headribbon.description>


  <!-- 래비 패션 모자 -->

  <RB_Fashionhat.label>Rabbie Beret</RB_Fashionhat.label>
  <RB_Fashionhat.description>A fashionable beret. While it makes the wearer more appealing, surprisingly it is also lined with aluminium to protect against psychic emenations.</RB_Fashionhat.description>


  <!-- 래비 겨울 목도리 -->

  <RB_Neckscarf.label>Rabbie Scarf</RB_Neckscarf.label>
  <RB_Neckscarf.description>A simple scarf. It helps keep the wearer warm.</RB_Neckscarf.description>


  <!-- 래비 야전군 전투복 A -->

  <RB_Infantryuniform.label>Rabbie Infantry Fatigues (Cargo)</RB_Infantryuniform.label>
  <RB_Infantryuniform.description>Camouflage fatigues typically worn by Imperial Empire forces. Bandoliers make reloading firearms easier, and kevlar padding protects against bullets.</RB_Infantryuniform.description>


  <!-- 래비 야전군 전투복 B -->

  <RB_Infantrynewuniform.label>Rabbie Infantry Fatigues (Tights)</RB_Infantrynewuniform.label>
  <RB_Infantrynewuniform.description>Camouflage fatigues typically worn by Imperial Empire forces. Bandoliers make reloading firearms easier, and kevlar padding protects against bullets.</RB_Infantrynewuniform.description>


  <!-- 래비 야전군 방탄재킷 -->

  <RB_Infantryvest.label>Rabbie Infantry Vest</RB_Infantryvest.label>
  <RB_Infantryvest.description>Camouflage vest typically worn by Imperial Empire forces. Bandoliers make reloading firearms easier, and kevlar padding protects against bullets.</RB_Infantryvest.description>


  <!-- 래비티시 야전군 방탄헬멧 -->

  <RB_Infantryhelmet.label>Rabbie Infantry Helmet</RB_Infantryhelmet.label>
  <RB_Infantryhelmet.description>Camouflage helmet typically worn by Imperial Empire forces. Lights and sensors on the helmet assist in aiming.</RB_Infantryhelmet.description>


  <!-- 래비 정규군 파워슈트 -->

  <RB_RegularInfantrySuit.label>Rabbie Power Armor</RB_RegularInfantrySuit.label>
  <RB_RegularInfantrySuit.description>A suit of light powered armor typically worn by Imperial Empire Marines. Reflective coating helps protect the wearer against energy weapons.</RB_RegularInfantrySuit.description>


  <!-- 래비 정규군 파워헬멧 -->

  <RB_RegularInfantryhelmet.label>Rabbie Powered Helmet</RB_RegularInfantryhelmet.label>
  <RB_RegularInfantryhelmet.description>A powered helmet typically worn by Imperial Empire Marines. Reflective coating helps protect the wearer against energy weapons. The visor has a heads up display that assist the wearer in aiming their shots.</RB_RegularInfantryhelmet.description>


  <!-- 래비 실무장교 제복 -->

  <RB_Subofficer.label>Rabbie Officer Coat</RB_Subofficer.label>
  <RB_Subofficer.description>An officer's coat in the style of the Imperial Empire. Provides modest protection, but is generally a decorative piece used to impress others.</RB_Subofficer.description>


  <!-- 래비 실무장교 베레모 -->

  <RB_Subofficerhat.label>Rabbie Officer Beret</RB_Subofficerhat.label>
  <RB_Subofficerhat.description>An officer's beret in the style of the Imperial Empire. Provides modest protection, but is generally a decorative piece used to bolster the wearer's resolve.</RB_Subofficerhat.description>


  <!-- 래비 고위장교 지휘복 -->

  <RB_SeniorOfficer.label>Rabbie Officer Uniform</RB_SeniorOfficer.label>
  <RB_SeniorOfficer.description>An officer's uniform in the style of the Imperial Empire. Provides modest protection, but is generally a decorative piece used to impress others and bolster the wearer's resolve.</RB_SeniorOfficer.description>


  <!-- 래비 고위장교 망토 -->

  <RB_HighCloak.label>Rabbie Officer Jacket</RB_HighCloak.label>
  <RB_HighCloak.description>An officer's jacket in the style of the Imperial Empire. Provides modest protection, but is generally a decorative piece used to impress others and stay warm in cold spacer environments.</RB_HighCloak.description>


  <!-- 래비 고위장교 지휘모 -->

  <RB_SeniorOfficerhat.label>Rabbie Officer Cap</RB_SeniorOfficerhat.label>
  <RB_SeniorOfficerhat.description>An officer's cap in the style of the Imperial Empire. Provides modest protection, but is generally a decorative piece used to impress others and bolster the wearer's resolve.</RB_SeniorOfficerhat.description>


  <!-- 래비 전력관리국 직원정장 -->

  <RB_Energymanager.label>Rabbie Formal Shirt</RB_Energymanager.label>
  <RB_Energymanager.description>A formal shirt and shorts attire in the style of the Imperial Power Management Bureau. Made of sterile fibers and equipped with tools that assist in caring for others and performing research.</RB_Energymanager.description>


  <!-- 래비 전력관리국 과학자 가운 -->

  <RB_Energygown.label>Rabbie Lab Coat</RB_Energygown.label>
  <RB_Energygown.description>A lab coat and attire in the style of the Imperial Power Management Bureau. The coat carries a small electric charge that wards off psychic emenations, and is equipped with tools that assist with the production of chemicals.</RB_Energygown.description>


  <!-- 래비 의사 진료가운 -->

  <RB_Inteligown.label>Rabbie Doctor Coat</RB_Inteligown.label>
  <RB_Inteligown.description>A coat and attire designed for rabbie doctors. Made of sterile fibers and equipped with tools that assist in providing medical treatment and the production of medicine.</RB_Inteligown.description>


  <!-- 래비 인텔리 안경 -->

  <RB_Glasses.label>Rabbie Glasses</RB_Glasses.label>
  <RB_Glasses.description>A set of rounded glasses. While unassuming at first glance, they are fitted with a microcomputer that assist the wearer with problem solving and seeing small details; which makes them helpful for treating injuries.</RB_Glasses.description>


  <!-- 래비 요리사옷 -->

  <RB_Cookwear.label>Rabbie Chef Apron</RB_Cookwear.label>
  <RB_Cookwear.description>A gown and apron set designed for rabbies. Insulated mittens and apron pockets help improve productivity while cooking</RB_Cookwear.description>


  <!-- 래비 요리모자 -->

  <RB_Cookhat.label>Rabbie Chef Hat</RB_Cookhat.label>
  <RB_Cookhat.description>A chef hat in the rabbie style. A subtle hairnet helps prevent food poisoning.</RB_Cookhat.description>


  <!-- 래비 기술자 점프슈트 -->

  <RB_Technician.label>Rabbie Jumpsuit</RB_Technician.label>
  <RB_Technician.description>A jumpsuit desinged for rabbies. Has lots of pockets for tools, helping improve productivity with mechanical crafting tasks.</RB_Technician.description>


  <!-- 래비 노동자 작업복 -->

  <RB_Handygirl.label>Rabbie Overalls</RB_Handygirl.label>
  <RB_Handygirl.description>A set of overalls designed for rabbies. The breezy design and pockets help improve productivity when building structures.</RB_Handygirl.description>


  <!-- 래비 안전모 -->

  <RB_Safehelmet.label>Rabbie Hard Hat</RB_Safehelmet.label>
  <RB_Safehelmet.description>A hard hat designed with rabbie ears in mind. Helps keep the ol' knoggin safe, and the light on the top helps with manual labour.</RB_Safehelmet.description>


</LanguageData>