<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

    <!--==================== Animal Stats ====================-->

    <NocturnalAnimals.BodyClock_Nocturnal>Nocturnal</NocturnalAnimals.BodyClock_Nocturnal>
    
    <!--==================== Animal Stats ====================-->
	
    <FF_PrimaryRole>Primary Role</FF_PrimaryRole>
    <FF_SecondaryRole>Secondary Role</FF_SecondaryRole>
    <FF_FunFacts>Fun Facts</FF_FunFacts>

    <!--==================== Roles ====================-->

    <FF_Floater>Floater</FF_Floater>
    <FF_Glower>Glower</FF_Glower>
    <FF_FunFact_1>Fun Firefly Facts</FF_FunFact_1>

    <!--==================== Role Descriptions ====================-->
	
    <FF_FloaterDesc>This animal floats above the ground, ignoring all movement penalties.</FF_FloaterDesc>
    <FF_GlowerDesc>This animal glows like a small sun.</FF_GlowerDesc>
    <FF_FunFact_1Desc>
        <li>
"Fireflies" are nocturnal members of the Lampyridae (Greek "to shine") family of winged beetles.
        </li>
        <li>
There are more than 2,000 species of fire flies. Not all of them glow.
        </li>
        <li>
Their light is created by a chemical reaction during which oxygen combines with calcium, adenosine triphosphate (ATP) and luciferin with the help of the enzyme luciferase.
        </li>
        <li>
Since the discovery of fireflies, scientists have also found ways to create synthetic luciferase. It is used primarily for food safety testing and forensic science.
        </li>
        <li>
Fireflies are the worlds' most efficient light source! 100% of the energy created is emitted through the light itself. In comparison, an incandescent light bulb emits roughly 10% of its energy as light.
        </li>
        <li>
Each species has a specific light pattern. Females will respond to males of their choosing with the exact same light pattern the male used.
        </li>
        <li>
Some species of firefly can sync up their light patterns. Photinus carolinus is the only North American species known to do this.
        </li>
        <li>
Each species has its own unique color to display. Some are yellow and orange, while others may be blue or green.
        </li>
        <li>
Fireflies are poisonous to certain other species of animal when digested.
        </li>
        <li>
The genus Photuris eat their own!
        </li>
        <li>
Their numbers are declining everywhere. Climate change, the harvesting of luciferase, light pollution, and habitat destruction are the main culprits. Fireflies do not migrate when their home is taken away from them. They simply disappear.
        </li>
    </FF_FunFact_1Desc>

</LanguageData>